《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
我弟弟是叛徒
My brother was a traitor.
他给我们下了诅咒
He poisoned us.
如果我能获得更多我的记忆
Perhaps if I can access more of my memories,
也许我能发现他的下一步行动
I might be able to uncover what his next move will be.
凯莉  你觉得我们能再深入
Kelly, do you think we can go deeper
研究黑曜石科技吗
with Obsidian's tech?
那样的能量会让你的大脑永久重置
That kind of power could re-set your brain for good.
我的移植能力在幻影区里被偷走了
The power to incept was stolen from me in the Phantom Zone.
那个女人给了你答案
That woman gave you the answer.
伊芙  这是霍普
Eve, meet Hope.
你们两个将会联合
You two are going to be working closely together.
我看穿你了  你是个破坏分子
I see you. You're a saboteur.
但这样的出人头地令人不齿
That's a rotten way of making it to the top.
贾罗德
Hey, Jarrod.
放我鸽子可不是好主意
Blowing me off was not a smart move.
我之前12次都没说清楚吗
Was I unclear the first 12 times?
我没有兴趣
I'm not interested.
如果你不和我们合作  下场可会很惨
If you don't work with us, this will end very badly.
你真要走威胁路线吗
You're going with threats?
你应该看看董事会每周二
You should see what my board threatens me with
是怎么威胁我的
every other Tuesday.
你这是在犯错
You're making a mistake.
超 女
第五季 第三集
谢谢你  詹妮
Thanks, Jenny.
下一次你姐姐要你当保姆
The next time your sister asks you to babysit,
直接拒绝就好
just say no.
记住  要划清界限
Remember, boundaries.
说到界限  你认识那女人吗
Speaking of boundaries, do you even know that woman?
我刚认识她  怎么了
I just met her, why?
她就这么告诉你她整个人生了
She just told you her whole life story?
我的工作基本上就是倾听  各位
It's kind of my job to listen, guys.
凯莉  你被变形者袭击了
Kelly, you were attacked by a shapeshifter.
他还在逃
And he's still out there.
而你派了所有超查部的特工去找他
And you have every DEO agent working to find him.
我觉得在目前情况下
I don't think it could hurt
最好还是低调点  直到他被抓住
to reel it in just until they catch him.
而作为艾丽克斯的妹妹
And as Alex's sister,
我可以告诉你  她几乎每次都是对的
I can tell you that she's almost always annoyingly right.
而作为凯莉的哥哥
And as Kelly's brother,
我可以告诉你  她可以保护好自己
I can tell you that she can handle herself.
听着  我不想打断这场丹弗斯与奥尔森大战
Listen, I hate to break up this Danvers-Olsen scrimmage,
但是我们要去开会了
but we have to get to our meeting.
-好吧  -试着别太担心
- All right. - Try not to worry so much.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
有马拉法克的迹象吗
Any sign of Malefic?
没有  看起来他也没有任何灵能信号
No. He doesn't seem to have any psychic signature either.
但我们会找到他的  必须找到他
But we'll find him. We have to.
你还好吗
You... You all right?
要跟莉娜吃午餐搞得我有些紧张
Maybe I'm a little nervous about having lunch with Lena.
这是在我告诉她我是超女后
It's the first time we're hanging out
第一次一起出去
since I told her I was Supergirl.
我骗了她那么久
I was just lying to her for so long.
卡拉  莉娜原谅了你
Kara, Lena forgave you.
你得卸掉过去的包袱
Okay? So you're going to have to just let go of the past.
我只想让我们之间的关系变好
I just want things to be great between us.
我希望这次午餐...
I... And I want this lunch to be--
完美
Perfect.
是的
Yes.
会的
And it will.
莉娜也希望你们的关系
Look, Lena wants your relationship
回到正轨上
back on track, too.
我得回超查部了
Look, I have to get back to the DEO.
你去其他地方做完美的人吧
You go be perfect somewhere else.
我尽力而为
I'll try.
好吧
Okay.
模拟失败
该死
Damn it!
你从黑曜石隐形眼镜里复制出的发讯器
The transmitter you duplicated from the Obsidian contacts
使用了目镜接口
uses an ocular interface.
鉴于你将它接入了大脑
Since you modeled it directly into the brain,
我建议你再把频率
may I suggest you lower the frequency
降低7.32%
another 7.32%?
不是这样的  霍普
It's not that, Hope.
理论上  Q波应该可以让我
In theory, Q-waves should allow me
重写人类大脑的一部分
to rewrite portions of the human brain.
消除这个世界的谎言  操控与暴力
To rid the world of lying, manipulation and violence.
是  但是不管我怎么调整频率
Yes, but no matter how I manipulate the frequency,
发讯器只能让我
the transmitter will only allow me
读取大脑的信息
to read information from the brain.
如果我想试着调整  就会出现僵化
If I try to augment it, I get a zombie effect.
而你不想要一个全是机器人的世界
And you don't want a world of robots.
你想要更好的人类
You just want better people.
是的
Right.
对不起  卢瑟女士
I am sorry, Ms. Luthor.
我这副模样
It must be uncomfortable,
还要你相信我  一定很不舒服
with me in this form, for you to trust me.
我不相信人类  霍普
I don't trust people, Hope.
我曾以为自己可以相信
I believed I could once.
我有几个朋友让我以为我可以
I had friends that made me believe I could.
但是他们像其他人一样背叛了我
But they betrayed me like everyone else.
你哥哥  莱克斯
Your brother, Lex,
是他们中最糟糕的
was the worst of them.
但是我认为他现在可以帮助你
But I believe he could help you now.
我拥有伊芙·泰斯马克的记忆
I have access to Eve Tessmacher's memories.
莱克斯之前在研究Q波
Lex was working with Q-waves.
这是他计划
It was part of his plan
穿透超人坚硬皮肤的一部分
to get past Superman's invulnerable skin.
他在私人日记里留下了详细记录
He left detailed records in his private journals.
他的日记
His journals?
一共有三本
There are three of them.
他们在五级安保设施峰脑堡垒中
They are currently in a level five secure facility at Fort Summit.
但是  经过进一步的分析
However, upon further analysis,
我们不可能拿到它们
retrieving them would be impossible.
卡拉发来新信息
我也许拿不到  但是
For me, maybe, but...
有人可以
not for everyone.
柳叶弯眉额上挂
Graceful arcs across her brow
留我思忖千万度
I'm left forever to wonder how
完美如你尼娅·纳尔
A being as perfect as my Nia Nal
-为何爱上渺小的我  -无法忍受这般的你
- Could ever love Someone as small... - Put up with this all.
你刚才说什么
What was that?
就是谢谢你的第一百...
Um, just thank you for poem one hundred and--
第一百二十七首诗
One hundred and twenty-seven.
一百二十七
是的  我就快精通十四行诗了
Yes, I've almost mastered the sonnet.
我认为你已经精通了
Oh, I think you've got it.
但你不应该过度精通
But you don't wanna overdo it.
说得对
You're right.
言以简洁为贵
Brevity is the soul of wit,
正如波洛尼厄斯对哈姆雷特所说
as Polonius said to Hamlet.
现在我将开始研究十九行诗
Now I shall move on to the villanelle.
这是一种更复杂的形式
A more complicated form,
但却能够表达更深层次的情感共鸣
but capable of much deeper emotional resonance,
正如迪兰·托马斯所写的
as exemplified by Dylan Thomas'
《不要踏入静谧的良夜》
"Don't go gentle into that good night--"
尼娅
Nia.
好了  下一个话题是什么
All right, what's next on the docket?
有明星离婚吗
Any celebrity divorces?
被喷的网红
Disgraced influencers?
我要看点击量
Show me the clicks.
我拿到了这星期的法医报告
I've got this week's medical examiner's report,
我认为我们可以报道一下近期的死亡事件
and I thought we could run a story on recent deaths.
人们喜欢阅读关于死亡的新闻
People love to read about death.
让他们记得自己还活着
It reminds them that they're alive,
并让他们有幸灾乐祸的感觉
and it gives them the pleasure of schadenfreude.
我喜欢
I like it.
二十岁网约车司机  被车撞死
Twenty-year-old Uber driver, hit by a car.
如果当事人很无聊
If the person is boring,
那死因也是无聊的
then the cause of death is boring.
来点惊人的  让人眼前一亮的死亡
Wow me. Show me some sparkly death.
不行  不行  不行
No, no, no...
奈尔斯·杰罗德  搞健康科技的亿万富翁
Dr. Niles Jarrod, a health tech billionaire,
刚刚被发现死在了夜店洗手间
recently discovered deceased in a night club bathroom.
我的天
My God!
杰罗德博士死了
Dr. Jarrod died?
我去年采访过他
I... I interviewed him last year --
为了那篇《基因操纵的道德意蕴》
For your piece on the moral implications of gene manipulation.
认识死者
Knowing the dead person
也不会让死讯更有趣
does not make their death interesting.
-下一个  -等等
- Next. - Wait, wait.
一位33岁的天才
A 33-year-old genius
在延长寿命领域有显著成就
doing significant work in the field of extending life
却意外英年早逝
dies young, unexpectedly?
多么悲剧
It's tragic.
这绝对值得一写
And certainly worth a story.
要么写重要新闻
There's hard news,
要么写正经专题或纯娱乐内容
legitimate feature, or brain candy.
而你刚刚提议的无病呻吟
Sentimental tripe you just pitched us
要单独另分一类  就是垃圾
is a category of its own... Trash.
你太过分了
How dare you --
威廉说得对
William's right.
死去的科学家毫无亮眼之处
A dead scientist is not sparkly.
也没有实质性故事
And there's no substantive story.
别再浪费我们的时间了
So stop wasting our time.
你怎么知道没有实质性故事
How do you know there's no substantive story
我们都还没有调查
when we haven't even looked into it yet?
我查过了  还很彻底
I've looked into it. Thoroughly.
什么内幕都没有
Nothing there.
弗兰克林
Franklin,
麻烦你换下一具尸体
next corpse, please.
完美
Perfect.
我认为关于杰罗德的报道你知道内幕
I think you know more about the Jarrod story,
出于某些原因  你不想让我报道
and for some reason you don't want me on it.
你太多疑了
You're paranoid.
你在楼上说谎了  为什么
You lied up there. Why?
别丢人了  丹弗斯
Stop humiliating yourself, Danvers.
真让人看不下去
It's painful to watch.
这个麻花辫我认识
I know that braid.
你还好吗
You okay?
我以为威廉·戴只是个野心勃勃的混蛋
Yeah. I thought I had William Dey pegged as an ambitious ass,
但现在我觉得他可能还要更坏
but I think he might be much worse.
-还记得我那篇遗传工程的文章吗  -记得
- You remember that piece I did on genetic engineering? - Yeah.
我的主要采访对象杰罗德博士
Well, my main subject, Dr. Jarrod,
死在了夜店里
was found dead in a club.
-吸毒过量吗  -还不清楚
- Overdose? - Unclear.
威廉·戴制止了这篇报道
And William Day spiked the story.
他说他已经调查过了
He said he'd already looked into it
根本没有任何内幕
and there was nothing more to find.
-有何不妥  -他在说谎
- So? - He was lying.
他的心跳快到爆表
His heart rate was through the roof.
关于杰罗德博士的死他知道些什么
He knows something more about Dr. Jarrod's death,
他不想让我查出来
and he doesn't want me to find out about it.
听起来我们该联系一下
Sounds like we should be calling
我在法医办公室的熟人
my contact at the M.E.'s office.
不好意思  "我们"
I'm sorry. We?
是的  我不想满脑子
Yeah. I mean, I want to get out of my head
只想着找工作的事  况且
about the job offers, and...
这或许是起待破获的凶杀案
We may have a murder to solve.
除非你不想要超级朋友帮忙
Unless you don't want a super friend.
怎么会  我当然想
No, of course I do.
那好  有新消息通知你
Okay then. I'll keep you updated.
好
Okay.
尼娅  快请进
Nia, come on in.
荣恩  怎么了  是关于马拉的事吗
J'onn, what is it? Is it Mal?
不不不  不是他的事
No, no, no. Nothing like that.
又一首诗
Another poem.
每天  每小时
Every hour of every day
布莱尼都会为一个新的身体部位写颂词
Brainy sends a new ode to a new body part.
抱歉  太不合时宜了
Sorry, um, not appropriate.
现在这也不重要
Or important, right now.
要我帮你什么
How can I help?
我想找回失去的记忆
I wanna restore my missing memories.
我希望你的梦境能力
I was hoping that you and your dream power
或许能比凯莉的技术更深入大脑
might go deeper than Kelly's technology could.
但扰乱记忆不是很危险吗
Isn't messing with memories dangerous?
不  我确信通过梦境找回记忆
No, I believe that restoring lost memories
应该是安全的
through dreams should be safe,
因为那是我自己通过自然的方法找回来
because I will be finding them myself in an organic way.
当然是在你的帮助下
With your help, of course.
荣恩  你确定你想记起来吗
J'onn, are you sure you want to remember?
马拉法克说我仍被蒙在鼓里
Malefic said I was still in the dark.
我认为他是对的
And I believe he's right.
那些遗忘的记忆之一
And one of those missing memories
有他背叛我们族人的关键原因
has the key to unlock why he betrayed our people.
他为什么要追杀每个我在乎的人
Why he's coming after everybody I care about.
假如我能真正明白发生过什么
If I can truly understand what happened,
我或许能阻止他
I might be able to stop him.
皮特·安德鲁斯
Pete Andrews?
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我多久没见过你了
I haven't seen you in, what?
有两年了吧
Like two years?
有个老战友在网上发文时
Well, one of the guys posted something online
提到你在这工作  我就来了
about you working here. So...
真奇怪  我刚刚入职
That's funny, I just started.
我刚好来城里
Well, I was in town,
就想来看看你和你的工作单位
I thought I might drop by and see your new digs.
真高级  奥尔森
Kind of fancy, Olsen.
谢了
Thanks.
老天  你能来真的太好了
God, it's so cool of you to stop by.
奥尔森博士
Dr. Olsen.
您一点半的预约到了
Your 1:30 appointment is here.
好的  真不好意思
Yeah. Ugh, I'm sorry.
我很想跟你叙旧  但现在真的不行
I would so love to catch up, I just, I can't right now.
凯莉  我是专程来纳欣诺市见你的
Kelly, I came to National City to see you.
我想
I think...
我想我需要帮助
I think I need help.
当然
Of course.
我最后一个预约大概六点半结束
My last appointment wraps up around 6:30.
你到时过来  我们再聊
Come back then, we'll talk.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你一直是这世界上最善良的人
You always had the biggest heart in the world.
谢谢
Merci.
再见
Au revoir.
你专程去香榭丽舍
You brought me coffee eclairs
在塞雷特街咖啡馆给我买了咖啡泡芙
from Cafe Rue Serret on the Champs-Elysees?
我知道这是你的最爱
I know they're your favorite.
还有卡布奇诺  你真的去了米兰的帕夫吗
And the cappuccinos, did you really go to Pave in Milan?
很快就回来了
It didn't take me that long.
要知道  我真的错过了好多
You know, I have really been missing out
跟超女做闺蜜所带来的好处
on the perks of having Supergirl as a best friend.
我们有好多错过的时光要弥补
Well, we have a lot of lost time to make up for.
是的  但你知道你不必专程飞去巴黎
Yeah, but you know you don't have to go to Paris
去买午餐  卡拉
to pick up lunch, Kara.
这对我来说不是最重要的
That's not what's important to me.
不过  这些都柏林的司康饼
But, these scones from Dublin,
我的天  我不介意你每天飞去帮我买
oh, my God, you can fly these in everyday.
跟我说说  凯特科最近怎么样
So, tell me, how is CatCo?
一切还好吗
Is everything okay?
安德里亚的表现还算得体吗
Is Andrea behaving civilized?
我可不会用这个词来形容她
That's not exactly the word I would use to describe her.
她一直以来的命令
Her mandate has been
让凯特科成了全世界浏览量最高的新闻网站
making CatCo the most viewed news website in the world
用的都是小测试和标题党这样的手段
using tactics like pop quizzes and clickbait.
卡拉  听你这么说我很遗憾
Kara, I'm so sorry to hear that.
是的  她还请了个名叫威廉·戴的奸诈小人
Yeah, and then she hired this snake named William Dey.
等等  威廉·戴  真的吗
Wait, William Dey? Really?
他应该是个才华横溢的记者
He's supposed to be a really talented journalist.
我知道  但是可惜
I know, but sadly,
才华并不总是意味着正直
talent doesn't always mean integrity.
我不知道他的作案手法
And I have no idea what his MO is,
但是  詹姆斯在帮我查
but James is helping me figure it out.
别再说我了  你好吗
Enough about me. How are you?
坦白说
To tell you the truth,
自从莱克斯的事之后  我过得不好
I haven't had the easiest time of it since Lex.
我一直在做恶梦
I've been having nightmares.
我尽量不睡
I try not to sleep.
莉娜
Oh, Lena.
夜晚都充满了我哥哥一手造成的
Nights are filled with apocalyptic visions of torture
末日般的折磨和痛苦
and anguish at the hands of my brother.
凯莉正在黑曜石之北治疗创伤后遗症的病人
Kelly is working with PTSD patients at Obsidian North.
也许她能帮你
Maybe she could help you.
谢谢  但你知道我是个非常注重隐私的人
Thank you. But you know how private a person I am.
知道
Yeah.
真正令人沮丧的是
You know, the really frustrating part is
我找到了治愈自己的方法
I figured out a way to heal myself.
你还记得我们在斯特赖克找到的日记吗
I mean, do you remember the journals we found at Stryker's?
当然
Of course.
看日记是唯一能让我冷静下来的事
Well, reading them is the only thing that calms me.
我一听到莱克斯的声音  疑团就解开了
Somehow, hearing Lex's voice takes the mystery away.
可怕也消失了
And the terror.
我知道如果我能把日记全部读完
I just know if I could read them all
那我就能治愈我的创伤
then I would be able to cure myself of the trauma.
那就把日记全部读完
Well, then that's what you have to do.
可惜这行不通
Unfortunately that is not an option.
莱克斯的物品全被政府没收了
The government has confiscated all of Lex's possessions.
他的技术和武器  甚至是童年日记
His technologies, his weapons, even his childhood journals.
太荒谬了
Well, that's ridiculous.
只有你对他的童年日记有兴趣
You're the only person that could have an interest in that.
你不能问他们拿回来吗
Can't you just ask for them back?
相信我  我试过了
Believe me, I have tried,
但却受制于官僚主义和繁文缛节
but it is all tied up in bureaucracy and red tape.
我律师说我不可能把日记从萨米特堡垒拿回来
My lawyer said I would never get them out of Fort Summit.
我可以帮你拿回来
Well, I could get them for you.
卡拉  别犯傻
Kara, don't be ridiculous.
日记能治愈你
The journals will help you heal,
只是因为技术性细则而被锁起来了
and they're only locked up due to a technicality.
我可以去拿回来  不会有人知道的
I could go and get them and no one would ever know.
不  我不能要求你这么做
No, I couldn't ask you to do that.
你没有要求
You're not asking.
我
I'm...
我自愿帮你
I'm offering.
是詹姆斯
Oh, it's James.
他在法医办公室
He's at the M.E.'s office.
没事  我们晚点聊
That's okay, we can talk later.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们有五分钟时间
Hey, we have five minutes.
好
Okay.
你没事吧  你怎么一副刚抢完银行的样子
You okay? You look like you robbed a bank.
抢银行
Robbed a bank?
绝对没有  我什么也不会抢
No, never. I would never rob anything.
只是一种比喻  卡拉
It's, uh... Just an expression, Kara.
好
Right.
一名健康的33岁男性
Okay, healthy 33-year-old male.
死因是心脏病突发
Cause of death, heart attack.
急救人员在市中心一家夜店洗手间的地上
EMTs found him unresponsive on the bathroom floor
发现他没有反应了
in a nightclub downtown.
上面有个东西
There's something there.
是一个
Is that a...
文身
tattoo?
在他的心脏里面
Inside his heart?
怎么在心脏上文身
How do you get a tattoo inside your heart?
这是塔费克利亚  喝起来有点怪
This is t'fek'lya. It may taste a little weird.
是火星人的一种草药  能帮助连接思想
It's a Martian herb which aids in the connection of minds.
不  味道很好
No, it's great.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
我们来吧
Let's do this.
抓住他  抓住他
Get him! Get him!
我不明白  这是什么
I don't understand. What is this?
他们为什么是人类形态
Why are they in human form?
我的潜意识以一种我能明白的方式
Your memories are being filtered through my subconscious
把你的记忆给过滤了
in a way that makes sense to me.
荣恩  等一下
J'onn, wait up.
荣恩  我觉得那个是你
J'onn, I think that's you.
我们来玩玩捉迷藏吧
Let's play hide and seek.
荣恩  你来找我们
J'onn, you're it.
我记得玩过这个游戏
I remember playing this game.
那里
There.
干得漂亮
Nice job.
马拉法克  轮到你找我们了
Malefic, you go now.
他不能连接集体思维
He cannot connect to the hive mind.
他做不到
He can't do it.
-你怎么回事  -他什么也做不了
- What's wrong with you? - He can't do anything.
住手  马拉法克
Stop it, Malefic!
睡吧
Sleep.
我以为白火星人
I thought the White Martians
用了某种科技
used some kind of technology
把马拉法克变成了可怕的武器
to turn Malefic into a terrible weapon,
但他生来如此
but he was born that way.
天生就能将自己的思想
Born able to project his thoughts
和意志投射到别人身上  但是
and his will on others, but...
以最残酷的方式把他与我的族人隔绝
cut off from my people in the cruelest way.
我们要去哪里  爸爸
Where are we going, Papa?
去一个没人能伤害你的地方  儿子
Where no one can hurt you, my son.
我英俊的儿子  要知道有人爱你
My beautiful son, know that you are loved
我们每天都会为你祈祷
and that we will pray for you everyday
你自己也必须祈祷
as you must pray yourself.
以赫隆米尔的教导为指导和治疗方法
Look to H'ronmeer's teachings for guidance and healing.
让他的忠告减轻你的痛苦
Let his counsel lighten your pain,
好把我们带到一个更美好的地方
so that he might deliver us to a better place.
父亲  荣恩
Father! J'onn!
别把我丢在这里
Don't leave me here!
我会乖的  我保证
I'll be good. I promise.
我们的神永远不会放弃你
Our god will never forsake you.
马拉法克  我爱你
Malefic, I love you.
求求你们
Please...
别丢下我  要我做什么都行
Don't leave me here. I'll do anything.
马拉法克  我是荣恩
Malefic, it's J'onn.
父亲每天都在为你的康复祈祷
Father prays for your healing everyday.
他有信心
He has faith that...
有一天你会回到我们身边的
one day you will return home to us.
赫隆米尔不是我的救星  哥哥
H'ronmeer is not my salvation, brother.
他们才是
They are.
赫隆米尔
H'ronmeer...
我辜负了我儿子  也辜负了你
I failed you as I failed my own son.
让白火星人把马拉法克征召进去
Allowed Malefic to be conscripted by the White Martians,
让议会把他送去炼狱
allowed the council to send him to that purgatory.
我心中的痛苦
The agony in my heart...
煎熬
It's...
万分
Unbearable.
我父亲痛苦不堪
In my father's anguish,
他一定是抹去了我们俩的记忆
he must have wiped both our memories.
把我弟弟从记忆中抹去了
Wiped my brother from existence.
荣恩
J'onn...
马拉法克当然会背叛他的族人
Of course Malefic turned against his own people.
他一定感觉到被人孤立和背叛
The isolation, the betrayal he must have felt.
他不是坏人  他只是个孩子
He wasn't evil, he was a child.
他需要我们的帮助
He needed our help.
然后我父亲走了  把他的记忆
And then my father goes and compounds the tragedy by...
从集体思维中抹去  从而加重了悲剧
wiping his memory from the collective.
对于火星人来说  死不是终结
For Martians, death isn't final,
抹去记忆才是
but erasing a memory is.
就像是我父亲
It's as if my father...
谋杀了自己的儿子
murdered his own son.
这些虚伪之举
And the hypocrisy.
他用一生
His whole life
去做一个高尚的人
was about being a holy man.
转而却犯下
And then he goes and...
这个族群最深重的罪恶
commits our culture's greatest sin.
饺子呢
Where are the dumplings?
糟糕
Oh, shoot!
我忘记下单了
I totally forgot to put the order in.
抱歉
Sorry.
我一直忙着调查
I just got caught up investigating
心上有纹身的男人离奇死亡案
the weird death of this guy with a tattoo on his heart.
好吧  我知道你为什么忘了饺子的事了
Okay. I can see why you forgot the dumplings.
原谅你了
All's forgiven.
还有麻烦呢
Yeah, but there's more.
威廉·戴对这事也有了解
William Day, he knows something about it,
他正拼命阻止我插手
and he actively tried blocking me from getting involved.
这报道听上去挺不错
Well, it sounds like a really good story, right?
这人向来喜欢跟你争
And this guy's always been very competitive with you.
你觉不觉得他是想自己独揽这条新闻
Do you think he's trying to just steal the scoop for himself?
可能吧  但我总感觉有点怪
Maybe. But something just doesn't feel right.
虽然我对这个心上带纹身的死者
As fascinated as I am by a dead guy
挺感兴趣  不过我更想
with a tattooed heart, I am far more interested
听你说说跟莉娜吃午饭的事
in hearing about your lunch with Lena.
怎么样
How did it go?
挺好的
It was great.
挺好
Great.
不是吧
Oh, no.
发生什么了
What happened?
没什么
Nothing.
我飞到巴黎  米兰  都柏林
I flew to Paris, Milan, Dublin,
买了各种她喜欢的东西
I got all of her favorite things.
所以
It was...
挺好的
Great.
那你怎么看起来跟出车祸撞到狗一样
So why does it look like you ran over a puppy?
没什么  真的  我
It was nothing. Really. I...
我只是  我答应要帮莉娜
I just... I kind of spontaneously agreed to...
一个忙
do a favor for Lena.
好  那有什么问题吗
Okay. So, what's wrong with that?
没有  就是需要我
Nothing. It just entails...
闯进军事基地
Breaking into a secure Army facility
偷莱克斯·卢瑟的日记
and stealing Lex Luthor's journals.
什么
What?
卡拉  你疯了吗
Kara, are you out of your mind?
我随口就答应了
I just blurted it out.
想也没想
I wasn't thinking.
可你该看看她有多痛苦
But, you should have seen how much pain she was in,
莱克斯的死带给她很大创伤
and she's so traumatized by Lex's death,
他的日记是她
and the journals are the only way
-唯一的安慰  -不行
- she can find closure. - No.
你现在马上打她电话
You're going to call her right now,
告诉她这事是你错了
and you're going to tell her that you made a mistake.
-你不会这么干的  -不行
- You're not doing it. - No. I can't.
不  你不能犯法
No. What you can't do is break the law
偷窃联邦财产
and steal federal property.
严格来说  我干的都是违法的事
Technically, I break the law all the time.
两个月前我就闯过超级监狱
I just broke into a supermax prison two months ago.
不  这完全是两码事
Okay. That is totally different.
那是为了维护正义  对吗
That's to serve justice. Right?
但这次你是为了朋友
Okay. What you're talking about here
以身试险
is crossing that line for a friend.
有什么区别
How is it different?
应该有人帮她走出悲伤
She deserves to heal,
况且这也不会伤害他人啊
and who would it be hurting?
你知道吗
You know what?
布莱尼为了帮我解决贾罗德博士的案子
Brainy just illegally hacked into security cameras
还非法盗取了夜总会的监控录像
at a nightclub to help me solve this Dr. Jarrod's murder.
你怎么没骂他
I don't see you scolding him.
完全是两码事
Totally different.
不过没错
But... Yes,
布莱尼不应该用超查部的技术
Brainy should not be using DEO tech
帮你写新闻
to help you write articles.
我会查清这件事的
I will crack down on that.
我就说一句
Just want to point out.
你觉得我们破坏规则这一套是跟谁学的
Who do you think we learned all this rule-breaking from?
这话伤人了
That cuts deep.
他就是贾罗德博士  还有威廉·戴
That's Dr. Jarrod, with William Day.
他在那里干什么
And what would he be doing there?
等等
Hang on.
我放大一下
Let me zoom in.
那是  蜘蛛
That's... the spider.
他心上的纹身
That's the tattoo on his heart.
你发现什么了  你认识那个女人吗
What do you see? Do you know that woman?
不  但
No. But...
我认识那种纹身
I know those tattoos.
凯特科全球媒体公司
跟我说说你的症状
So, tell me what you're going through.
偏头痛
Migraines.
恐慌
Panic attacks.
在坎大哈被狙击手压制
Well, getting pinned by snipers in Kandahar
会扰乱你的心智
is hard on the psyche.
我不是以前的我了
I'm not the same person I was before.
阿富汗带走了我的一部分
Afghanistan took something from me.
我大脑里有东西破裂了
Something in my brain is broken.
我想把它找回来
And I want it back.
你能帮我吗
Can you help me?
我周五有空
I have an opening this Friday,
可以开始接收流程
and we'll start the intake process.
可能需要几个月来确认你的资格
It can take a few months to qualify--
不行
No!
我太
Oh, I'm so...
凯莉  我等不了了
Kelly, I can't wait.
我现在情况危急
I'm in crisis now.
如果不能解决现状
If I don't get a handle on this...
我恐怕会伤害自己
I'm scared I'm gonna hurt myself.
我不会让你伤害自己的  彼得
I am not going to let you hurt yourself, Pete.
你要明白
You have to understand...
事情没那么简单
it's not that simple.
我工作刚上任  而且还有规定
My job is new, and then there's protocol...
凯莉  求你帮帮我
Kelly, please help me.
办公室一小时后人就不多了
The office will thin out in an hour,
我把你偷偷带进去
and I'll sneak you in later.
然后开始诊断
We'll start with the diagnostic,
我会给你答复
and get you some answers.
但是彼得
But Pete...
我们在这件事上必须低调
we have to keep this on the down-low.
-行吗  -没问题
- Is that okay? - Oh, of course.
你救了我的命
You're a life saver.
你有心事
Something is bothering you.
没  没什么
No, it's nothing.
不对  你瞳孔放大了
Your pupil dilation says otherwise.
你都可以告诉我
You can tell me anything.
布莱尼  如果你有很重要的事情
Brainy, if you had something
要告诉某个人  但是
really important to tell someone, but...
如果说出来了  对方会很伤心
if you did tell them, it would hurt them very much,
你还会说吗
would you still do it?
我的经验是
In my experience...
你如果在乎对方  就该告诉对方事实
if you care about someone, you should tell them the truth.
不管事实多残酷
However painful,
说出来对彼此都好
both of you will be better for it.
如果你还是不开心
If you are still feeling blue,
我可以给你念首诗
I could cheer you up with a poem.
"致尼娅·纳尔左耳垂的颂歌
"An Ode to Nia Nal's Left Earlobe.
-十九行诗"  -不要
- A Villanelle--" - No!
拜托不要
Please, no.
你有事情想告诉我吗
Is there something you wanted to tell me?
没有
No.
但我有事情要告诉荣恩
But there is something that I have to tell J'onn.
这不是纹身
They aren't tattoos.
这是奥拉费人
This is an Aurafacian.
一种附在宿主身上的外星生物
This is an alien organism that attaches to a host body.
这是原宿主
This is the original host.
这个奥拉费人是莱克斯
This Aurafacian was one of the aliens
从我们的废弃设施转移出去的外星人之一
that Lex had transferred out of our desert facility,
很明显还在逍遥法外
and obviously is still at large.
它可以改变身形  变成纹身
It can transform back and forth between a tattoo
或者是三维生物
and a three-dimensional creature,
因此她格外危险  也难以阻挡
making her uniquely dangerous and very hard to stop.
现在...
Now...
看看我们的新宿主
Meet our new host.
-有身份信息吗  -好
- Can we get an ID? - Yeah.
我看看
And...
找到了
Bingo.
卡洛琳·奥康纳
Caroline O'Connor.
她曾经是特殊行动队长
She's former special ops command,
擅长近战  爆炸物
she's highly rated in hand-to-hand combat, explosives,
而且还是狙击手
and she's a sniper.
她两年前销声匿迹
She went off the radar two years ago,
不知怎么跟我们的外星人联系上了
and somehow hooked up with our alien.
所以有人雇她杀贾罗德
So somebody hired her to kill Jarrod.
对  不过是谁  为什么
Yeah. But who? And why?
她可真是费尽心思掩藏踪迹
Well, someone went a long way to cover her tracks.
纳欣诺市西藤大道19号
还不够
Not far enough.
我们拿到了地址
We just got an address.
我不会让她再伤害其他人了
I'm not gonna let her hurt anyone else.
藏在梳妆台后面的闪存盘
A flash drive hidden behind a dresser?
我似乎没请你来这里
I don't think I invited you here.
我不请自来
I invited myself.
没错  我早有准备
Yeah. I came prepared.
詹姆斯
James!
卡拉
Kara!
这个设备利用磁共振效应
This device uses magnetic resonance
能够吸出他们墨水中的重金属
to attract the heavy metals in their ink.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
好了
Yeah.
我们正在检查奥康纳公寓里的证据
We're examining the evidence from O'Connor's apartment,
包括你找到的外部闪存盘  超女
including the external drive you located, Supergirl.
我正在试图解开上面的加密
I am simultaneously attempting to break the encryption on it,
但这项加密技术很复杂
but... it is far more complicated
比接下来一千年内的都要棘手
than anything I've seen in the next 1,000 years.
好  我来把这些收起来
All right. Let's get these down into holding.
你还好吗
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
我还遇到过更激烈的袭击
I've been hit harder than that.
你本不必这么做的
You didn't have to do that.
你现在有这么多事要忙
With everything you have on your plate,
还要竞选参议员...
your potential run for Senate...
如果她真的伤了你怎么办
What if she really hurt you?
朋友有难  出手相助  仅此而已
When your friend's in trouble, you jump in, period.
结果无所谓
Doesn't matter the consequences.
你好好休息
You keep resting.
告诉艾丽克斯和布莱尼  我马上回来
Tell Alex and Brainy that I'll be right back.
如果奥康纳有新消息  可以联络我
I'll be on comms if they get a lead on O'Connor.
好
Okay.
你要去哪儿
Where you going?
去帮一位朋友
To help a friend.
很晚了  你还好吗
It's late, you all right?
我有东西要给你看
I need to show you something.
是你梦境的后续  火星上的那件事
It's the rest of your dream about what happened on Mars.
你没有看到的部分
The part you didn't see.
你想看看吗
Do you want to see it?
因为会让你很难受
Because it's going to be painful.
当然
Absolutely.
赫隆米尔
H'ronmeer...
我辜负了你  也辜负了我的儿子
I failed you as I failed my own son.
我心中的痛苦
The agony in my heart...
已经
It's...
难以承受
Unbearable.
父亲  你已经为马拉尽了全力
Father, you did the best you could for Mal.
这不怪你
It's not your fault.
他是我儿子
He was my boy.
我的孩子
My child.
他控制不了他的病
He could not control his illness.
这是我的考验  而我失败了
The test was mine and I failed!
我不配活着
I do not deserve to live.
如果我自己一无所成
And how can I continue to counsel our people...
凭什么指导我的子民
when I myself am nothing.
父亲  我们的子民需要你
Father, our people need you.
我也需要你
I need you.
那我就辜负了所有人
Then I have failed everyone.
赫隆米尔  原谅我
H'ronmeer, forgive me.
是我干的
It was me.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我把他从我们的脑海中删去了
I erased him from our minds.
我几乎是亲手杀了我弟弟
I as good as murdered my own brother.
你是为了救你父亲
To save your father.
是为了救我们
To save us both.
我...
I had, uh...
我当时找我父亲是寻求帮助
I had gone to my father to seek counsel.
想要减轻我自己的痛苦
To ease my own pain.
看到他那样
And seeing him like that...
我没有想办法让他打起精神
Rather than finding the strength to lift him up,
反而
I, uh...
反而犯下了
I crossed a line
在我的文化里不能原谅的罪过
that's unforgivable in my culture.
过去的三百年里
I spent the last 300 years...
我一直在赎罪  因为我逃离了火星
trying to repent for having fled Mars...
现在却发现
only to find out
那简直是我最轻的罪名了
that is the least of my sins.
我无颜面对任何人
Oh, I am so ashamed.
你那样做是出于同情
You did it out of compassion.
出于善意
Out of goodness.
你父亲心如刀割
Your father was heartbroken.
而你拯救了他
You saved him.
我父亲
My father
宁愿死也不会愿意失去宝贵的记忆
would rather die than have his holy mind wiped.
我那样做是为了自己
What I did, I did for myself.
你必须向我发誓
You must swear to me...
永远不会跟任何人提起
you will never speak of what you saw...
你看到的事
to anyone.
我发誓
I swear.
这些会扫描你的大脑
These will scan your brain
读取你的记忆
and read your memories.
你的记忆会出现在这个屏幕上
And your memories will appear on this screen.
你  你能看到我的记忆吗
You... You can see my memories?
我是为了帮助你接受它们
Just so I can help you process them.
我会帮你保密的
Everything's confidential.
好  但是...
Okay, but...
我的记忆就会
So, they're just gonna...
直接同步出现吗
appear there in real time?
会稍微有点延迟
Uh, no, there's a bit of a lag.
整体布局需要几分钟
It takes a few minutes for the mapping to finish
图像处理器也需要时间
and the image generators to do their thing.
别担心
Don't worry.
你会做得很好
You'll do great.
开始吧
Let's do it.
峰脑堡垒
超女
Supergirl?
布莱尼解开了奥康纳闪存盘上的加密
Brainy cracked the encryption on O'Connor's drive.
她的下一个目标是安德鲁·斯特恩博士
Her next target is Dr. Andrew Stern
在纳欣诺市医院  我们在过去的路上
at National City Hospital. We're en route.
我这就过去
I'm on my way.
超女  我找到他了  我们在正厅
Supergirl, I got him. We're in the atrium.
斯特恩博士  我们有证据表示
Dr. Stern, we have reason to believe
你已经被人盯上  成了暗杀目标
that you are the target of an assassination attempt--
斯特恩博士
Dr. Stern?
漂亮
Nice shot.
你真是开始招我烦了
You're really starting to bug me.
你就是他
You're him.
紧急警戒
我的移植能力  可以用了
My inception power. It worked.
凯莉出事了
It's Kelly.
你在为谁卖命
Who do you work for?
艾丽克斯
Alex!
她死了
She's dead.
是什么杀了她
What just killed her?
谢谢你  人类
Thank you, human.
你恢复了我的能力
You have returned my power.
什么  你在对我做什么
What? What are you doing to me?
这是幻影区夺走的我的能力
This is the power that the Phantom Zone took from me.
控制你思维的能力
The power to control your mind.
这要感谢你的软弱了
You can thank your weakness for this.
为了表示感谢  我会让你死得痛快
In gratitude, I'll grant you a quick death.
不
No...
求你了
Please.
马拉法克  不
Malefic! No!
不  赫隆米尔的诅咒
No! H'ronmeer's curse.
如果你追杀我
你自己也会死的
我知道你所忍受的一切
都怪我
我为自己对你所做的感到抱歉
你忘记了我
你把我放逐了三百年
你夺走了我的一切
我现在知道了
但你应该冲着我来  别伤害我朋友
你自找的
-不许动  -救我  他们要杀我
- Freeze. - Help. They're trying to kill me.
他在那里  那个咖啡师
There he is. The coffee guy.
不不不  等等  在那边  那个清洁工
No, no, no, wait. There he is, the janitor.
你看得见我吗
You can see me?
凯莉  小心
Kelly, look out.
他逃走了
He's gone.
怎么了
What happened?
马拉法克来找她了
Malefic came after her.
我的通灵扫描没有发现严重创伤
My psychic scan shows no serious signs of trauma.
但似乎Q波的释放
But it would seem the release of Q-waves
与黑曜石科技的相互作用
somehow interacted with Obsidian's tech
在凯莉和马拉法克的思维中建立了一种联系
and forged a link between Kelly's mind and Malefic's.
即使在他变身时  她也能看见他
She could see him, even when he shapeshifted.
如果她能看见他
Well, if she can see him...
那她对马拉法克就是个威胁
Then she's a threat to him.
恐怕情况更糟
I'm afraid it's even worse than that.
我弟弟现在有了火星人的移植能力
My brother now has the Martian power to incept.
让你违背自己的意愿听从他的指令
Make you do the things he wants you to do against your will.
他还会来对付她
He'll come after her again.
他会来对付你们所有人
He'll come after all of you.
你知道他为什么做这些事吗
Have you been able to figure out why he's doing this?
因为他背叛了族人  我把他关进了幻影区
I put him in the Phantom Zone for betraying my people.
他应该是想报仇
I guess he just wants revenge.
听着  我很抱歉因为我和你们的关系
Look, I'm sorry that your association with me
置你们于危险之中
has put you all in danger.
对付马拉法克是我的责任
Malefic is my responsibility.
眼下
Right now...
我们要把凯莉送到安全的地方
we need to get Kelly to safety.
让她离开是我们最佳选择
Taking her off the board is gonna be our best bet.
那样的话我就能集中注意力
That way I can focus all of my attention
集中超查部的所有资源去找他
and our DEO resources on finding him.
你想我离开吗
You want me to go away?
是的  等我们抓住他为止
Yes. But just until we catch him.
我觉得艾丽克斯是对的
I think Alex is right.
别担心  我会陪着你  好吗
But don't worry, I will stay with you. Okay?
不  你有自己的决定
No, you've got decisions to make.
我不想让你错失良机
I don't want you missing out.
但我最关心的就是你
But you are my priority.
你今晚就走
You should leave tonight.
荣恩那边怎么样
How did it go with J'onn?
很好
Good.
结果不是什么大事
Turned out not to be that big of a deal.
我能感觉到你有烦恼了
I can sense that something is weighing on you.
十九行诗是最能鼓舞士气的
Well, nothing lifts the spirit like a villanelle--
别说了
Stop.
你让我说实话  即使它会伤你的心
You said I had to be honest even if it hurts your feelings,
所以事实是
so here's the truth.
这  这太多了  好吗
It's just... too much. Okay?
从现在起  没有食物  没有诗歌
From now on, no more food, no more poems,
什么都不能有
no more anything.
我知道
I know...
你本意是好的
that you mean well.
我知道你所处的环境  这很甜蜜
I know where you're coming from, and it's... sweet.
这一切都很甜蜜  只是我...
It's all so sweet. I... I just...
这一切都太多了
It's too much.
你  你让我做自己
You... You asked me to be myself.
在你面前完全做我自己
To be completely myself with you.
但现在你又说你不想要了
But now you tell me you don't want that.
我只能百分百运行
I can only operate at 100%.
我就是这样制造出来的
That's just how I'm built.
这完全是我的问题
Which is entirely my problem...
跟你无关
and not yours.
布莱尼
Brainy.
我听说了贾罗德的事
I heard about Jarrod.
是的
Yeah.
我不知道我还能坚持多久
I don't know how much longer I can keep this all going.
坚持下去
Keep at it.
再祝你好运
And good luck.
你说得对
You were right.
我太直率  太轻信他人了
I was too open and too trusting.
全都怪我
It's all my fault.
但愿它们管用
I hope they help.
它们已经管用了
They already have.
我希望我们没有越界
I hope we haven't crossed any boundaries?
没有  对你这样的朋友没有界限可言
No, for a friend like you there are no boundaries.
别告诉你的目的地  好吗
Don't tell me where you're going, all right?
这样更安全
It's going to be better that way.
-好  -谢谢你  詹姆斯
- Okay. - Thank you, James.
这个
Here.
拿着
Take this.
这是莱克斯的物质传送门手表
It's one of Lex's transmatter portal watches.
别问我怎么拿到的
Don't ask me how I got it.
如果有麻烦  直接用
Just... If there's trouble, just use it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
一切都会好起来的
Everything is going to be okay.
我要找到马拉法克  然后带你回家
I'm going to find Malefic and I'm going to bring you home.
-再见  -小心驾驶
- Bye. - Drive safe.
你说一切都会好起来
You know, you say everything's going to be fine,
但我知道那个表情
but... I know that face.
你不相信
You don't believe it.
我爱她的直率
Look, I love the fact that she's so open.
只是让我太害怕了
It just scares the life out of me.
或许  事情没有那么糟
Well, maybe... maybe it's not so bad,
一切都会好的
and it will all work out.
我和莉娜就和好了
It worked out with me and Lena.
希望如此吧
I hope so.
希望我们俩都好
For the both of us.
你找到你要找的东西了吗
Did you find what you need?
你看看
Take a look.
告诉我你看见了什么
Tell me what you see.
莱克斯的童年日记
Lex's childhood journals.
没看见原理图或任何技术性的东西
Not seeing schematics or anything technical.
这是莱克斯版本的维吉尼亚密码
It's Lex's version of a Vigenere cipher.
这是一个复杂的多字母代换
It's a deceptively complex polyalphabetic substitution.
我现在看懂了
I see it now.
现在开始破译
Deciphering now.
如何利用Q波进行思想控制
作者  莱克斯·卢瑟
在过去十年中
科学家们已经使用Q波技术来治疗脑外伤
现在我知道我要做什么了
Now I know what I have to do.